What makes you so sure that your life is worth more than those people out there on the ice?  Is it the money?
是什么让你如此确信   你的生命比那些冰上的人的生命更有价值  是钱吗
The accident of birth puts you inside the big fancy house?
还是你出生在一座巨大的豪华房子中的巧合
I help move this country forward.
我帮助国家发展
I move this empire forward.
我推动这个帝国发展
Human progress isn't measured by industry.
人类的进步不是以工业成就衡量的
It's measured by the value you place on a life.
是以对生命的重视程度衡量的
An unimportant life.
一条不重要的命
A life without privilege.
一条没有特权的命
The boy died on the river, that boy's value is your value.
那个死在河上的男孩   那个男孩的价值是你们的价值
That's what defines an age. That's...
那定义了一个时代   那
...what defines a species.
定义了一个种族